

Brad Preston

5261 W. W Ave Schoolcraft, MI 49087 (269) 823-2628 bap5393@gmail.com https://bradpreston.dev

Skills

I'm a web developer with 5 years of practice and 1 year of professional experience. My preferred stack is Next JS, Sass, TypeScript, and MongoDB. I have used React, Svelte, Express JS, Node JS, PHP, and Laravel in both practice and professional settings.

Experience

July 2021 - PRESENT

Brod Solutions, Mattawan, MI- Web Developer

- Build and maintain features for our clients ecommerce stores
- Maintain in-house Process Pro API software
- Help train developers

Freelance

Kazoo 48 Film Festival, Kalamazoo, MI - Freelance Web Developer

- Designed, built, and hosted https://kazoo48.com
- Tech used: Next JS, Sass, TypeScript, Stripe, and Vercel

Freelance

Parrot Distro, Kalamazoo, MI - Freelance Web Developer

- I assisted in setting up the store and built some custom pages/components for https://parrotdistro.com
- Tech used: Stencil, Handlebars, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, BigCommerce

Freelance

Aaron's Music Service, Vicksburg, MI- Freelance Web Developer

- Designed, built, and hosted https://aaronsmusicservice.com
- Maintain and update the site upon request
- Tech used: Svelte, HTML, CSS, Render

January 2019 - March 2021

Presidential Safe and Security, Kalamazoo, MI- Locksmith/Security

- Installed and repaired locksets
- Installed and setup security camera systems
- Maintained a key management software

Education

2007 - 2011

 ${\bf Vicksburg\, High\, School, Vicksburg, MI-\it Diploma}$

Socials

Linkedin- https://www.linkedin.com/in/brad-preston/

GitHub- https://github.com/BradPreston

Twitter- https://twitter.com/BradDoesCoding